[music]
>> Running [music] in the sand.
Living on the land. [singing]
The salty breeze [music] was in our
eyes. We stood beneath the dragonflies
and danced [music]
all
night.
We polished all the chrome
on a rusty little [music] home.
We slept all night in parking lots. We
tied our hearts [music] in double knots
so tight.
So free.
>> [music]
>> So [singing]
bright.
Remember [music]
when
we were just cherubs in our tender
[music]
skins
waiting patiently for love
>> [music]
>> to begin?
>> Flowing so free.
Blowing [music] in the breeze.
The songs we sung [singing] so long ago
with whiskey [music] and an afterglow,
we shine
like
[music]
new.
>> [music]
>> But there along the way
something seemed to change.
As weeks turned [music] into months, we
knew as life caught up we slowly grew
[music]
apart.
And untied
our
hearts.
>> [music]
>> Remember
when
>> [music]
>> we were just children
in our tender skins,
waiting patiently [music]
for love
to
begin?
But the summer went away and the skies
went [music] gray.
We slowly ran
out of things to say.
The river turned into
drought.
Our time was fading [music] out.
Defeated and lonely, we returned back
home. Like a bird without a wing, we
would never float
away
into a
>> [music]
>> suspended dream.
>> Remember
when
>> [music]
>> you walked away in the
December
wind?
I felt the stinging [music] on my pale
skin.
I [music] knew that things would never
be the same
again.
>> [music]
>> Remember
when
the clouds rolled in and
the sunlight [music]
>> [singing]
>> dimmed?
And what we'll be [music] like that
would matter
forever.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Mhm.